ENTER ZIP CODE

update zip code

OR

use my location

1. [Home](https://www.ashleyfurniture.com/)
2. [Privacy Policy](https://www.ashleyfurniture.com/privacy-policy)

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Who We Are
----------

We are not just a furniture store. While Ashley® is the most iconic segment of the Ashley brand today, the Ashley family of companies is much more than just a retail store. Ashley Furniture Industries, LLC is the largest manufacturer of furniture in the world with major manufacturing facilities in the United States and abroad. Ashley Furniture Industries supplies furniture to over 6,000 retail partners in 123 countries. Ashley Distribution Services, Ltd. delivers over 30 million pieces of that furniture annually with its gigantic fleet of trucks and trailers while also providing backhaul services to many other companies. Ashley Global Retail, LLC operates Ashley and Ashley Outlet retail furniture stores throughout the United States and  [www.ashley.com](http://www.ashley.com/) , the Ashley retail website.

Scope of this privacy policy
----------------------------

This is the privacy policy of Ashley Furniture Industries, LLC, Ashley Distribution Services, Ltd., Ashley Global Retail, LLC, and their respective affiliates (collectively referred to as “Ashley,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), and it describes how and why we collect, use, share, and protect your personal information within our Ashley and Ashley Outlet retail stores in the United States and on our websites and mobile services. Our privacy policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect, use, and share your personal information. Personal information is information that directly or indirectly identifies, describes, relates to, is reasonable capable of being associated with, or can reasonably link to a particular consumer or household.

Please note that many Ashley retail locations are independently owned and operated and have their own privacy policies. Additionally, we maintain separate privacy policies for our international operations, and we may provide different notices of our information practices with respect to certain subsidiaries or affiliates, in which case this privacy policy will not apply.

The information we collect about you
------------------------------------

The information we gather about you depends on the context. By and large, it’s information about you that can personally identify you—either on its own or when combined with other information.

The following describes the information we collect and how we obtain it.

_Information we collect from you_

* For registration. When you create an account through one of our websites or mobile services (our “sites”), we collect your name, email address, and phone number. Once you’re registered, we assign you a unique ID number. This ID number helps us recognize you when you’re signed in.
* For billing and delivery. To process payments and deliver products you order, we collect and use your payment information. This can include your name, your address, your telephone number, your email address, your credit or debit card information, and any other relevant information.
* For user-generated content. We may offer you the ability to post content that other users can read (e.g., product reviews) on our sites or social media pages. Anyone can read, collect, and use any personal information that accompanies your posts. We do not have to publish any of your content. If we are required by applicable law to take down, remove, or edit your personal information, we will comply to the required extent.
* For contests, sweepstakes, and special offers. When you sign up for these, you give us your name, email, and any other required information.
* For surveys. We gather information through questionnaires, surveys, and feedback programs. We ask you for your consent to use this information when you participate in these surveys and programs.
* During contact with our call centers. We collect information from you when you place an order over the phone or contact customer care through one of our toll-free numbers.
* Through online chat. We collect information from you when you communicate with us through the online chat tool on  [www.ashley.com](http://www.ashley.com/) and the Ashley mobile app.
* Personal contacts data. We never scan your device for your contacts or upload that data. With your consent, we do comply with your requests to collect data about your friends, family, or acquaintances (e.g., Refer a Friend campaigns). This functionality is only meant for U.S. residents. By using it, you acknowledge and agree that both you and your contacts are based in the U.S.—and that you have everyone’s consent for us to use their contact information.

* Through your camera. Certain features of our sites may ask you to grant us access to the camera on your computer or mobile device (such as image search, augmented reality, or scanning bar codes).

_Information collected automatically_

You also provide us information in other ways through technology. Some of this information may be linked to you personally.

* These technologies include cookies, web beacons, tags and scripts, software development kits (or SDKs) and beyond. We track and store data about how you visit and use our sites. The items we log include:
    * Your IP address
    * Your location
    * Your operating system
    * Your browser
    * Your browser language
    * The address of referring websites
    * The URLs of any pages you visit on our websites and mobile apps
    * Device identifiers
    * Advertising identifiers
    * Other usage information

We combine this data with other information we collect about you. For more information about tracking methods on our sites, and how to manage them, see “Cookies and Other Trackers” below.

If your browser doesn’t accept our cookies, you may not be able to access all or parts of our sites. Because the “Do Not Track” browser-based standard signal has yet to gain widespread acceptance, we don’t currently respond to those signals. However, we do respond to the  [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) .

* With GPS features. We may collect information about your location when your device is set to provide location information. For example, your device’s GPS signal allows us to show you the nearest Ashley locations. We may be able to recognize the location of a mobile device in stores where we provide customers free WiFi access or through the use of Bluetooth technology. Through mobile services, Bluetooth technology in our stores allows us to show you nearby products that may interest you, making it easier for you to locate products within and navigate through the store.

* With facility cameras. We operate cameras in store for security and operational purposes, for example, to help us improve the design of our stores to better serve our customers.

_Information we collect from other sources_

We receive information about you from other sources so that we can fulfill orders for our products that you have placed with third party retailers and to help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, and prevent or detect fraud. Examples of information we receive from other sources include:

* Purchase, delivery, and address information from third party retailers that sell our products and then send us the product orders to fulfill;

* Updated delivery and address information provided by our carriers;

* Account information from third party lenders or lease-to-own service providers to enable us to complete your purchases;

* Public data, survey data, and demographic data from privately-owned databases; and

* Social media platform data, including aggregate data on our followers (e.g., age, gender, and location), engagement data (e.g., “likes,” comments, shares, reposts, and clicks), awareness data (e.g., number of impressions and reach), and individual users’ public profiles.

Below is a table showing the categories of personal information that we collected during the preceding 12 months and identifying for each category the source categories for that information, the business or commercial purposes for collecting that information, and the categories of third parties with whom we share that information.

| Category of Personal Information | Source Categories | Business or Comercial Purposes | Categories of Third Parties With Whom We Share Information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers such as a real name, postal address, physical address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, IP address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, or other similar identifiers | * Provided by you from forms or direct interactions<br>* Collected by us through your interactions with our sites<br>* Provided by independently owned and operated Ashley retail locations<br>* Provided by third parties for whom we fulfill orders of our products<br>* Data brokers or resellers<br>* Social media services, like Twitter or Facebook | Complete your request to sign up to receive information via email from us<br><br>Complete your request to register as a member of any of our websites<br><br>Process and complete your purchase or other transaction<br><br>Provide you with customer service, including scheduling and tracking deliveries, scheduling in-store appointments, and answering questions about our products<br><br>Process and resolve product warranty claims<br><br>Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you<br><br>Respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us<br><br>Protect the security and integrity of our sites and business<br><br>Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations, and statutes | To help us perform the business and commercial purposes set forth in this table, we may share your personally identifiable information with:<br><br>* Ashley retail locations that we don’t control. Many Ashley retail locations are independently owned and operated. We work closely with these independent Ashley retail locations to perform the identified business and commercial purposes.<br><br>* Third party service providers. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, providing customer service, and measuring ad performance. |
| Personal characteristics, such as your gender, age, date of birth, citizenship status, marital status, and veteran or military status | * Provided by you from forms or direct interactions<br>* Data brokers or resellers<br>* Social media services, like Twitter or Facebook | Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you<br><br>Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations, and statutes |     |
| Commercial information, including records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies | Provided by you from forms or direct interactions<br><br>Collected by us through your interactions with our sites<br><br>Provided by independently owned and operated Ashley retail locations<br><br>Provided by third parties for whom we fulfill orders of our products | Fulfill orders of our products made through third parties<br><br>Provide you with customer service, including scheduling and tracking deliveries, scheduling in-store appointments, and answering questions about our products<br><br>Process and resolve product warranty claims<br><br>Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you<br><br>Respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us<br><br>Protect the security and integrity of our sites and business<br><br>Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations, and statutes |     |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement | Collected by us through your interactions with our sites | Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you<br><br>Respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us<br><br>Protect the security and integrity of our sites and business<br><br>Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations, and statutes. |     |
| Geolocation data | * Collected by us through your interactions with our sites | Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you<br><br>Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations, and statutes |     |
| Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this subdivision to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes |     | Customize your shopping experience using technology like algorithmic recommendations and machine learning<br><br>Notify you of advertisements and promotions using the internet, email and mail sent via the U.S. Post Office<br><br>Communicate great values and featured items to you |     |

Other situations in which we may share your information
-------------------------------------------------------

Sometimes we use marketing vendors to market our products, stores, and sites to you. We serve ads through websites, locations, platforms, and services operated and owned by third parties. Often these ads are targeted at people who have visited our sites but have not purchased anything. The ads are also targeted at people with similar traits or behaviors to our customers. We target our advertising to these users by uploading an encrypted customer list to a third party, or by incorporating tracking technology from a third party onto our sites. The third party then matches individuals who appear in both our data and their data. Because of how this matching process works, the third party can’t read our encrypted customer list if they don’t already have it. To opt out of receiving these matched ads, contact the applicable third parties. For example, when we use a “Custom Audience” to serve you our ads through Facebook, you should be able to hover over the box in the right corner of that Facebook ad and opt out. We are not responsible for any third party’s failure to comply with opt-out requests.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that all or a part of our business is merged, sold or reorganized (including transfers made as a part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings), personal information about you could be shared with the successor business.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To enforce or apply your contractual obligations to us, including for billing and collection purposes.

* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ashley, our customers, or others.

### Sale of Information

We do not sell personal information of our customers as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. But certain data privacy laws broadly define “sell” to include the sharing of personal information with third parties in exchange for something of value, even if no money changes hands. For example, sharing an advertising or device identifier to a third party may be considered a “sale” under certain data privacy laws. Under that broad definition of “selling” personal information, we have “sold” personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding 12 months. _For more information, see table above_ .

### What about Sensitive Personal Information?

We generally don’t want to gather any sensitive information about you. We would prefer that you never share with us any sensitive information, including:

* Your social security number
* Your racial or ethnic origin
* Your political opinions
* Your religion or other beliefs
* Your health, biometric, or genetic characteristics
* Any trade union membership
* Any criminal background

### How Long Do You Retain Data?

It depends. We store your personal information for as long as needed, or permitted, based on the reason why we obtained it (consistent with applicable law).

Children
--------

Our sites are intended for a general audience and are not directed at children under thirteen (13) years of age. We do not permit anyone who tells us they are under the age of 13 to register or open an account with us. We also do not collect information from anyone that tells us they are under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children’s online activities and use parental controls or other web filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the internet.

Cookies and Other Trackers
--------------------------

_What cookies and other trackers do we use?_

We use cookies and similar tracker methods when you visit our sites.

* A cookie is a small string of text that a website (or online service) stores on a user’s browser. It saves data on your browser about your visit to our sites or other sites. It often includes a unique identifier. “First-party cookies” are cookies set by us (or on our behalf) on our sites. “Third-party cookies” are cookies set by other companies (such as Google) whose functionality is embedded into our sites. “Session cookies” are temporary cookies stored on your device while you visit our sites. They expire when you close your browser. “Persistent cookies” are stored on your browser for a period of time after you leave our sites. Persistent cookies expire on a set expiration date, or when they are deleted manually. You can choose whether to accept cookies by editing your browser settings. However, if cookies are refused, your experience on our sites may be worse, and some features may not work as intended.

* Pixels (also known as “web beacons,” “GIFs” or “bugs”) are one-pixel transparent images located on web pages or messages. They track whether you have opened these web pages or messages. Upon firing, a pixel logs a visit to the current page or message and may read or set cookies. Pixels often rely on cookies to work, so turning off cookies can impair them. But even if you turn off cookies, pixels can still detect a web page visit.

* JavaScript is a programming language. It can be used to write trackers that, when embedded into a page, allow us to measure how you interact with our sites and other sites.

* SDKs are pieces of code provided by our digital vendors (e.g., third-party advertising companies, ad networks, and analytics providers) in our mobile apps to collect and analyze certain device and user data.

* Device identifiers are user-resettable identifiers comprised of numbers and letters. They are unique to a specific device. They are stored directly on the device. They are used to recognize you and/or your devices(s) on, off and across different apps and devices for marketing and advertising purposes.

In order to decide what type of ad might interest you, our digital and marketing vendors sometimes link data—inferred from your browsing of other sites or collected from other sources—using a method known as “ID synching” or “cookie synching.” To do this, they match the tracker ID they have assigned to you with one or more tracker IDs that are held in another company’s database and that are likely also associated with you. Any of the linked trackers may have certain interests and other demographic information attributed to it. That information is then used to determine which ad to show you.

The types of trackers that appear on our sites include:

* **Essential trackers** required for our sites to operate. They allow you to navigate one of our sites and use its services and features (e.g., cookies that help you stay logged in). Without essential trackers, our sites will not run smoothly and our sites, or certain services or features, might not even be available to you simply because of technical limitations.

* **Preference trackers** allowing us to store information about your choices, settings and preferences. They also help us recognize you when you return to our sites, remember your language settings (among others) and customize our sites accordingly. They are not essential to the functioning of our sites.

* **Analytics trackers** collecting or using information about your site use, which helps us improve our sites. Among the uses of analytics trackers are to show us which pages are most frequently visited, help us record difficulties you have with our sites, and track purchases and behaviors leading to purchases. These trackers add up our customers’ visits to show us larger patterns in our customers’ behavior. We look at these larger patterns to analyze site traffic.

* **Marketing trackers** help us determine which ads or content to show you, both on our sites and on other sites. To do this, these trackers use information about your behavior on various sites to target our ads and content. These trackers allow us to limit the number of times you see our ads and content across your devices. They help us personalize the ads and content we show you. They also enable us to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

_You can manage trackers._

You can refuse or accept trackers from our sites (or any other site) in your browserʼs settings. We also respond to the  [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) , which you can use to refuse trackers. If you refuse trackers, you might not be able to sign in or use other tracker-dependent features of our sites.

To opt out of Google Analytics data collection, follow Google’s instructions at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

To reset your device identifier, follow  [Google instructions](https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/answer/6048248?hl=en) and  [Apple instructions](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223) .

The ad agencies and other vendors with which we work may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative. To opt out of interest-based advertising from the participating companies, please visit  [NAI Mobile Choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice/) or  [AppChoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) . Note that opting out through these channels does not mean you will no longer see ads and is specific to the device and browser you are using. You will still receive other types of ads from these companies, and any type of ad from nonparticipating companies. The sites you visit may still collect your information for other purposes.

Security
--------

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of the data you provide to us. Our servers are protected by firewalls and are physically located in secure data facilities to further increase security. While no computer or facility is 100% safe from outside attacks, we believe that the steps we have taken to protect your personally identifiable information dramatically reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate for the type of data involved.

Email
-----

You may receive email messages from us. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, let us know by following the opt out directions on any of the email messages you have received from us. Please note that if you wish to opt out of receiving emails from independently owned and operated Ashley retail furniture stores you will need to contact them directly to communicate your contact preferences.

Notice Of Financial Incentives
------------------------------

We may offer various financial incentives and benefits (such as free shipping, discounts, and other special offers) to customers who interact with us in our stores or via our sites and provide certain personal information to receive the stated incentive or benefit. Generally, for any financial incentive we offer, we do not assign monetary or other value to personal information; however, the value of the personal information provided by you is reasonably related to the estimated value of the relevant financial incentive for which the information was collected. We reserve the right to withdraw or modify the financial incentives we offer at any time. The terms of the incentive will be presented to you at the time you sign up.

Your Data Rights, Including Access, Deletion, and Opt-Out
---------------------------------------------------------

You have the right to request that we disclose to you what information we collect, use, disclose, and sell. You also have the right to request that we delete any personal information about you which we collected about you. To submit either of the above requests, click and complete the form at  [https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com](https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com/) , send an email to  [privacyoffice@ashleyfurniture.com](mailto:privacyoffice@ashleyfurniture.com) , or call 800-757-0064. We reserve the right to deny your request if we cannot verify your identity. Please note that third party apps that send marketing unsubscribe requests by bulk emails may be blocked by our security filters, so we recommend that you use our customer preferences tool at  [https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com](https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com/) instead of using a third party unsubscribing app.

You have the right to direct us to not sell or share your personal information. Just click and complete our Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information request located  [https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com](https://preferences.ashleyfurniture.com/) , send an email to  [privacyoffice@ashleyfurniture.com](mailto:privacyoffice@ashleyfurniture.com) , or call 800-757-0064.

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of these data rights.

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request to exercise your rights on your behalf. Your authorized agent must be able to provide to us all of the information that we would otherwise require to verify your identity. For your protection, we reserve the right to deny any request from an agent who does not submit proof that they have been authorized to act on your behalf. 

Applicable laws may give you additional rights that are not described in the Privacy Policy.

California Privacy Rights – “Shine the Light”
---------------------------------------------

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of California Civil Code, a California resident with whom we have established a business relationship has the right to request from us certain information with respect to the types of personally identifiable information we have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third parties, and the identities of the third parties with whom we have shared information during the immediately preceding calendar year. All requests for such information must be in writing and sent to: Ashley Privacy Office—Legal Department, 1670 E 8th Ave., Tampa, FL 33605.

Concerns About Privacy
----------------------

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us:

Ashley Privacy Office—Legal Department  
1670 E 8th Ave.  
Tampa, FL 33605

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

As we continue to improve the services, products, and features we provide, our privacy policy is subject to change. Our privacy policy is subject to change without direct notice to you. We may change our privacy policy at any time by posting a new version of it on our websites. Therefore, you should review our privacy policy each time you visit any of our websites. The dates provided below will inform you as to when the most recent material updates to our privacy policy occurred and the date on which our updated privacy policy became effective.

Date of Last Update: August 3, 2023

Date Updated Policy Became Effective: August 3, 2023

By using this site you agree to our use of session replay tools to collect real-time information about your use of our site. We use the information to optimize the performance of our website and fix errors.

Yes No

_Envelope_ Sign up and get $50 off^† your first purchase!

 Sign Up

About Ashley
------------

Ashley Help
-----------

Services
--------

Legal
-----

Design Resources
----------------

* * *

© Ashley Global Retail, LLC, 2024. All rights reserved. [Sitemap](https://www.ashleyfurniture.com/ashleysitemap/)
